Greg Riveroll

8014 Timberlodge Trail, Centerville, OH 45458 | (858)465-6739 | griveroll86@gmail.com

Overview

Former correctional professional with over six years experience as a Correction Officer and Storekeeper in a state government, maximum security facility. In addition, over 10 years experience providing customer service, inventory management and control.

Core Competencies

- Excellent interpersonal communication skills
- Motivated to work as a team leader or member, with or without direct supervision
- Reliable and dependable
- Organized and detail oriented

Experience

Dayton Correctional Institution

Storekeeper, January 2019 - July 2021

- Order and maintain inventory from approved vendors.
- Operate point-of-sale transactions for inmate shoppers.

Correction Officer, June 2015 - January 2019

- Supervise inmates and enforce departmental or institutional rules and policy.
- Ensure the safety and security of staff, inmates and institution.
- Accurately complete all reports.

True North Energy

Customer Service Representative, February 2006 - June 2015

- Operate cash register.
- Stock, rotate, front and face store shelves and extra stock.
- Inventory, label and organize various products.

Education

OSU Web Development Boot Camp, January 2022

Ramona High School, High School Diploma, May 2004

Certificates

ServSafe, Crisis Intervention Team, CPR and First Aid